Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Here we go! Into the Shadow Palace!
In order to save the souls of those who had reincarnated as elves, Asta and the others stormed the Shadow Palace.
These paintings... Hey there.
It's Ryl. Here's an idea! How about I wake you up right now?
Inside the Shadow Palace, Asta and Mimosa encountered Ryl, while Noelle met Fauna.
You again? I don't understand this. Why are you here?
I may be Fauna, but I'm a much different Fauna than the one you remember.
I'm about to teach you the importance of respecting your elders, you mangy brat!
Meraleona faced off with Vedo, and Voigolion with Kaiser.
Both found themselves in a heated battle.
Begone!
You're mine, human!
Not me!
I must prove it!
I have to be strong!
prong!
let's not tellin' it
so
Centering
don't
get
and
I
Thank you.
Now, now, to love me, love!
How did I lose her?
I may not be using my Valkyrie armor to its fullest potential yet, but I can still maneuver
better than she can.
She must be Fauna the Hateful in her final form, the one who also possessed Fauna of
the Diamond Kingdom.
In that case...
Up until this moment, I've been afraid of using its full power, focusing on control
instead and holding back in my strikes.
Now it's time to go all out!
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragons!
Dwarf!
Ah!
Flame recovery magic.
Phoenix robe.
Oh wow, that attack was pretty intense, and it appears I've lost my clothes again.
Pretty neat, huh?
The forbidden magic we used allows us to draw on the power of the other world to cast supernatural spells.
This isn't good.
Apologies, I was getting kinda sick of dying.
How am I supposed to win against that?
Plant magic.
Magic cannon flower!
Never ends!
Oh man, no time to switch into my dark form.
And even if I could pull it off, if I can't land a hit on Rill, what's the point?
What's this? Oh, you're still alive?
This isn't going well.
Thanks, Osta. I'm so sorry. I'll heal you.
Thanks, but it doesn't look like we're gonna get a break anytime soon.
I know. Mimosa, hop up onto my back, then use some vines to tie us together.
Huh?
Combining's the only chance we've got here!
What? Combining?
Hurry!
Uh, right!
Plant recovery magic!
Princess healing flower round!
Okay then!
Come at us!
Like, help!
Shago dessa now!
We'll have to pass you, Mimosa.
Oh!
Whoopee!
That's no good.
This group of elves is especially strong.
We've gotten close, but we haven't managed to strike a decisive blow just yet.
Sorry you missed me!
It's magic!
Expand your mana zones. Form magic paths.
Everyone, join the magic knights already fighting.
Focus your energy on supporting them with long-range offensive spells.
Right, let's go!
He's so... he's beautiful. His looks are no match for mine, but still, he's just stunning.
There's no way. How could he gather all the magic knights scattered throughout the kingdom so quickly? It's not possible.
Yuno!
I'm so glad you're here!
I made this! Please, help yourself!
This doesn't seem like the time.
Yeah, now shoot! What are you doing here anyway?
Heh heh heh. The castle was in trouble, so I came to offer my culinary services.
This food... it can restore my magic.
Thank you. That's amazing.
He said it was amazing!
My friend liked his provisions! I could die, Happy!
What's going on?
Well, you see, Asta and the Captains are fighting the ultimate battle against all the enemy's strongest team members inside that pitch-black castle.
But unfortunately, the entrance is already closed.
So Asta's fighting in there.
That lies. What do you think it is?
Hey! Let's go! Get away from Yuno this instant!
But he hasn't even had his dessert yet!
Oh, shut your mouth! I'll be his dessert!
I vow to follow you to the ends of the world and cook you delicious food!
Sit tight, Asta.
Wait, am I seeing things?
Asta's hot rival friend just got inside.
Yeah, so did Charmy.
No fair.
You know, where can't you run off to?
And what was that weird place we just went through?
Also, where am I now?
Oh, I'm in hell!
What the actual heck is this place?
Charmy?
Asta!
How did you get in?
Uh, I have no idea!
I was just saying no to Yuno, trying to beat him, but now I'm here!
Ah!
Uh, Yuno's inside too?
Where could you have gone to, Yuno?
What is all of this?
These monsters are spells!
We'll drew all of them!
We have to do something to stop him!
Is that...
Charmy?
Oh no.
That's not it.
It just isn't right.
This isn't what I want.
I drew some monsters because I thought they'd be a fitting end to humanity.
But in fact, I actually want to draw something prettier.
That's the truth.
I don't want to create art like this.
It's so ugly.
This is all the humans' fault!
They did this!
Look at you.
You're all upset.
Maybe you're in a bad mood because you're hungry.
Huh?
A little food might calm you right down, here.
When did she...
Shut up!
Get away from me, you cretin.
I would never eat anything that was made by human hands.
Rude.
Who do you think you are?
Cotton creation magic.
Strike the sleeping sheep.
If I want to create, I must first destroy.
I'll tear them down.
The humans and everything they've built.
She's...
Shardy, no!
Are you okay?
Wait.
What's going on?
What is this mama?
Is...
Is it her?
Hey.
Can I come out now?
What is this magic?
It's not normal.
It doesn't feel...
Entirely human.
No way!
Why did she get bigger?
This seems familiar.
I felt this magic before.
It means...
You were born to a human and a dwarf.
And you have characteristics of both.
You're a hybrid.
So she's a human?
And a dwarf?
Wait.
You...
You're saying I'm by dwarves?
She didn't know either!
Hold on just a second!
What even is a dwarf?
What are they?
Dwarves are...
Well, I only know from the folk tales our elderly butler used to tell us, mind you.
They lived separate from the elves.
But like them, they're a race from long ago who possessed special powers.
Whoa, hold on!
Weren't you a sheep just a minute ago?
Shut up!
When did you learn to speak?
At the moment, that's the least of our concerns.
Well, I admit you have a point.
We can talk later.
I'm starving.
So let's eat.
You are so annoying.
And half-dwarf or no, if you think that you can stand in my way, I'll disappear you!
Yeah...
Make more monsters, elf.
My appetite's insatiable!
Food magic!
Let's banquet!
Whoa!
That thing is eating magic!
Aren't her spells usually a lot fluffier?
This isn't good.
I've heard of this before.
That hybrids can end up with two distinct magical attributes.
Now what?
When that wolf eats my magic, it becomes hers.
And it's eating so fast, way faster than I can draw.
I refuse to let your appetite wipe out my imagination, you hear me?
I'll make you regret it.
Nobody wastes the food I make!
Eat this!
That's for the protein!
And this, that one's for the fat!
I know they're just punches enhanced by magic, but they're so powerful!
And now, this is for the wasted carbs!
Oh, you cannot be serious.
Do you actually imagine this could be enough to get rid of my hate between humans?
Yeah?
I'm not even close to being done!
This is for the vitamins!
This is for the fiber!
This is for the collagen!
This is for the...
What is happening?
Uh, she's totally lost it!
Hey, Asta!
You go on ahead!
I gotta found a legend about wasting perfectly good food into this jerk's brain!
We better hurry.
Okay, we're counting on you, Charmy!
Just leave it to me!
Mimosa, which way?
There were a number of paths before, but a few of them have gotten blocked because of all the crazy fighting.
If we could go up...
We should try getting out that way!
Right!
I'm sorry!
You can't win, no matter how much you attack!
Get ready, because I'm gonna reduce you to ashes real soon!
I never thought I'd say this, but...
I miss Asta!
Asta!
Kiki!
Well, well, well!
This chick seems like she wants to get sliced!
Did it really have to be you?
Excuse me!
Are you telling me we got a problem here, little girl?
Huh?
Who's that?
It's David!
He's a fellow member of the Golden Dawn.
He was possessed by an elf like most of the squad was.
Guess somebody already knocked him out.
Alright, lucky break.
There are faint traces of magic here.
I can sense them now.
But it's weird.
It doesn't seem to belong to humans or elves.
What's going on?
I'll use Magic Flower Guidepost again.
What's this?
Underneath the strongest point,
there's a space with something in it
that looks like a pedestal.
There seem to be three elves there.
And I think that magic might be...
It's Yuno!
Let's go then!
Wait for me, Yuno!
Well, this is quite a surprise.
We sent Ato's group to pick you up,
but instead,
you took them out and got here on your own.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I'm glad you were able to get here safely and all that,
so congrats.
Hand over that magic stone.
Immediately, please.
I've been waiting...
for this moment.
As usual, Rone,
you're so quiet
that I can't even understand what you're saying.
Finally,
everything we've lost will be restored,
including our future.
And...
licked the smile.
Light creation magic!
Light swords of conviction!
Copy, light magic!
Mono-zone.
Spirit's hushed dance!
What's this?
How did he manage to evade all those attacks?
Mono-zone.
Spirit storm double!
In the time it took to get here,
he managed to level up his power,
both as a human and as an elf.
This kid.
In terms of sheer talent,
he might surpass even Lish.
I don't understand why my monosome couldn't detect him.
It wasn't super speed.
He just suddenly appeared.
Again!
No.
He made me move.
He can forcibly change someone's position.
Even if he's only touched them once.
I don't know if it's a magic stone or not,
but that belongs to me.
Give it back.
Nice job, Rone.
I see you're still as quick as always.
No one could ever beat you a tag.
And now,
we can finally make things right?
Indeed.
Hmm.
I can tell when someone's lying.
And I wonder why you told a lie just now, Rone.
What's going on?
Who the hell are you?
Don't tell me.
This reincarnation,
it can't be.
Subtitle sure does great work.
I can't take care of you.
He trailed itself.
What did you go to?
Even before it began,
He saw what we felt too.
He didn't turn to turn.
Thank you.
This is a famous paradox you see. You all should think about it too.
Are you a liar?
That guy isn't Rone.
This magic.
Who could this man be?
Next time on Black Clover, page 115, Mastermind.
Wait, what have we even been trying to do this whole time?